var quizArray = [{
		"id":"0",
		"question":"How many years an Alligator can live?",
		"choice1":"100",
		"choice2":"50",
		"choice3":"120",
		"choice4":"70",
		"correct":"100"
	},
	{
		"id":"1",
		"question":"What is the most famous bird in North America?",
		"choice1":"Vulture",
		"choice2":"Peacock",
		"choice3":"Turkey",
		"choice4":"Hawk",
		"correct":"Turkey"
	},
	{
		"id":"2",
		"question":"If male rabbits are called *bucks*, then female are called?",
		"choice1":"Hare",
		"choice2":"Bunny",
		"choice3":"Rabbit",
		"choice4":"Does",
		"correct":"Does"
	},
	{
		"id":"3",
		"question":"How many stomachs does a cow have?",
		"choice1":"1",
		"choice2":"2",
		"choice3":"3",
		"choice4":"4",
		"correct":"4"
	},
	{
		"id":"4",
		"question":"How many years does cat lived with humans?",
		"choice1":"10,000 years",
		"choice2":"5,000 years",
		"choice3":"12,000 years",
		"choice4":"7,000 years",
		"correct":"7,000 years"
	},
	{
		"id":"5",
		"question":"What is the dumbest dog in the world?",
		"choice1":"Afghan Hounds",
		"choice2":"Chihuahua",
		"choice3":"Shih Tzu",
		"choice4":"Boston Terrier",
		"correct":"Afghan Hounds"
	},
	{
		"id":"6",
		"question":"How many muscles are there in a cat ear?",
		"choice1":"44",
		"choice2":"25",
		"choice3":"32",
		"choice4":"41",
		"correct":"32"
	},
	{
		"id":"7",
		"question":"How many pecks can a woodpecker do per second?",
		"choice1":"20",
		"choice2":"30",
		"choice3":"15",
		"choice4":"25",
		"correct":"20"
	},
	{
		"id":"8",
		"question":"How many muscles does a garden caterpillar have in its head?",
		"choice1":"150",
		"choice2":"138",
		"choice3":"220",
		"choice4":"248",
		"correct":"248"
	},
	{
		"id":"9",
		"question":"An elephant can smell water up to how many miles away?",
		"choice1":"5",
		"choice2":"3",
		"choice3":"9",
		"choice4":"1",
		"correct":"3"
	},
	{
		"id":"10",
		"question":"On average, how many times does a cow poop per day?",
		"choice1":"16",
		"choice2":"13",
		"choice3":"19",
		"choice4":"11",
		"correct":"16"
	},
	{
		"id":"11",
		"question":"How many times does a whale heart beats in a minute?",
		"choice1":"9",
		"choice2":"15",
		"choice3":"21",
		"choice4":"27",
		"correct":"9"
	},
	{
		"id":"12",
		"question":"How many times does a humming bird beats its wing per second?",
		"choice1":"40-50 times",
		"choice2":"50-60 times",
		"choice3":"70-90 times",
		"choice4":"60-80 times",
		"correct":"60-80 times"
	},
	{
		"id":"13",
		"question":"How many taste buds does a dog have?",
		"choice1":"1,200",
		"choice2":"1,350",
		"choice3":"1.700",
		"choice4":"1,550",
		"correct":"1,700"
	},
	{
		"id":"14",
		"question":"How many cows does it takes to supply NFL with enough leather for a year's supply of footballs?",
		"choice1":"2,200",
		"choice2":"3,350",
		"choice3":"2,700",
		"choice4":"3,000",
		"correct":"3,000"
	},
	{
		"id":"15",
		"question":"Where is the hippopotamus born?",
		"choice1":"Dessert",
		"choice2":"Green Land",
		"choice3":"Underwater",
		"choice4":"River",
		"correct":"Underwater"
	},
	{
		"id":"16",
		"question":"How many insects can a bat eat in an hour?",
		"choice1":"1,000",
		"choice2":"1,200",
		"choice3":"980",
		"choice4":"890",
		"correct":"1,000"
	},
	{
		"id":"17",
		"question":"How many stray dogs live in New York City Metropolitan Area?",
		"choice1":"1,000,000",
		"choice2":"1,200,000",
		"choice3":"9,800,000",
		"choice4":"8,900,000",
		"correct":"1,000,000"
	},
	{
		"id":"18",
		"question":"How many muscles does an elephant trunk have?",
		"choice1":"12,100",
		"choice2":"14,400",
		"choice3":"15,000",
		"choice4":"13,350",
		"correct":"15,000"
	},
	{
		"id":"19",
		"question":"What is the most popular female dog name?",
		"choice1":"Maggie",
		"choice2":"Marj",
		"choice3":"Marie",
		"choice4":"Mary",
		"correct":"Maggie"
	},
	{
		"id":"20",
		"question":"What is the most popular male dog name?",
		"choice1":"Max",
		"choice2":"Stay",
		"choice3":"Mark",
		"choice4":"Katz",
		"correct":"Max"
	},
	{
		"id":"21",
		"question":"A large group of goats is called?",
		"choice1":"Herd",
		"choice2":"Army",
		"choice3":"Group",
		"choice4":"Peer",
		"correct":"Herd"
	},
	{
		"id":"22",
		"question":"Squirrels cannot see the color?",
		"choice1":"Red",
		"choice2":"Blue",
		"choice3":"Green",
		"choice4":"Yellow",
		"correct":"Red"
	},
	{
		"id":"23",
		"question":"How many eggs does an average chicken lays per year?",
		"choice1":"255",
		"choice2":"260",
		"choice3":"310",
		"choice4":"220",
		"correct":"260"
	},
	{
		"id":"24",
		"question":"How many eggs percent of cheetah cubs make it to adulthood?",
		"choice1":"5-10%",
		"choice2":"10-15%",
		"choice3":"20-25%",
		"choice4":"5-15%",
		"correct":"5-10%"
	},
	{
		"id":"25",
		"question":"How many hours does ferret sleep a day?",
		"choice1":"15",
		"choice2":"18",
		"choice3":"20",
		"choice4":"16",
		"correct":"20"
	},
	{
		"id":"26",
		"question":"Birds can recognise:",
		"choice1":"Landmark",
		"choice2":"Humans",
		"choice3":"Color",
		"choice4":"Things",
		"correct":"Landmark"
	},
	{
		"id":"27",
		"question":"What animal is capable of turning its stomach inside-out?",
		"choice1":"Humming Bird",
		"choice2":"Octopus",
		"choice3":"Starfish",
		"choice4":"Lobster",
		"correct":"Starfish"
	},
	{
		"id":"28",
		"question":"Sharks have been around longer than:",
		"choice1":"Dinosaurs",
		"choice2":"Whales",
		"choice3":"Walrus",
		"choice4":"Lobster",
		"correct":"Dinosaurs"
	},
	{
		"id":"29",
		"question":"About two-thirds of shark attacks on humans have taken in water less than what feet deep?",
		"choice1":"8feet",
		"choice2":"10feet",
		"choice3":"6feet",
		"choice4":"12feet",
		"correct":"6feet"
	},
	{
		"id":"30",
		"question":"Sharks are immune to what illness?",
		"choice1":"Cancer",
		"choice2":"Cold",
		"choice3":"Fever",
		"choice4":"Headache",
		"correct":"Cancer"
	},
	{
		"id":"31",
		"question":"Alligator cannot?",
		"choice1":"Move Backwards",
		"choice2":"Jump",
		"choice3":"Run",
		"choice4":"Turn",
		"correct":"Move Backwards"
	},
	{
		"id":"32",
		"question":"What is the most popular dog breed in Canada, America, and Great Britain?",
		"choice1":"Siberian Husky",
		"choice2":"Boston Terrier",
		"choice3":"Labrador Retriever",
		"choice4":"Golden Retriever",
		"correct":"Labrador Retriever"
	},
	{
		"id":"33",
		"question":"What is the weight of the largest giant squid ever found?",
		"choice1":"8,000 pounds",
		"choice2":"7,500 pounds",
		"choice3":"8,200 pounds",
		"choice4":"7,900 pounds",
		"correct":"8,000 pounds"
	},
	{
		"id":"34",
		"question":"Approximately, how many people died when they are stepped on by cows?",
		"choice1":"100",
		"choice2":"150",
		"choice3":"200",
		"choice4":"250",
		"correct":"100"
	},
	{
		"id":"35",
		"question":"How many eyes does a butterfly have?",
		"choice1":"10,000",
		"choice2":"11,000",
		"choice3":"12,000",
		"choice4":"13,000",
		"correct":"12,000"
	},
	{
		"id":"36",
		"question":"Among all living creatures, what makes the loudest sound?",
		"choice1":"Lion",
		"choice2":"Humpback Whale",
		"choice3":"Giraffe",
		"choice4":"Hippopotamus",
		"correct":"Humpback Whale"
	},
	{
		"id":"37",
		"question":"What is the color of hippo's sweat?",
		"choice1":"White",
		"choice2":"Red",
		"choice3":"Pink",
		"choice4":"Transparent",
		"correct":"Pink"
	},
	{
		"id":"38",
		"question":"50% of whale milk is composed of?",
		"choice1":"Fat",
		"choice2":"Protein",
		"choice3":"Iron",
		"choice4":"Zinc",
		"correct":"Fat"
	},
	{
		"id":"39",
		"question":"The swan has over _____ feathers in its body.",
		"choice1":"25,000",
		"choice2":"30,000",
		"choice3":"32,000",
		"choice4":"35,000",
		"correct":"25,000"
	},
	{
		"id":"40",
		"question":"Giraffes have no:",
		"choice1":"Kidney",
		"choice2":"Vocal Cords",
		"choice3":"Lungs",
		"choice4":"Diaphragm",
		"correct":"Vocal Cords"
	},
	{
		"id":"41",
		"question":"Starfish have __ eyes- one at the end of each legs.",
		"choice1":"Eight",
		"choice2":"Seven",
		"choice3":"Nine",
		"choice4":"Six",
		"correct":"Eight"
	},
	{
		"id":"42",
		"question":"There are almost _______ dogs in the United States.",
		"choice1":"60 million",
		"choice2":"50 million",
		"choice3":"45 million",
		"choice4":"55 million",
		"correct":"60 million"
	},
	{
		"id":"43",
		"question":"How long is the tunnel can a mole dig in one night",
		"choice1":"290 feet",
		"choice2":"320 feet",
		"choice3":"300 feet",
		"choice4":"340 feet",
		"correct":"300 feet"
	},
	{
		"id":"44",
		"question":"Where does French Poodle originate?",
		"choice1":"France",
		"choice2":"Germany",
		"choice3":"England",
		"choice4":"Paris",
		"correct":"Germany"
	},
	{
		"id":"45",
		"question":"The breeding of male goats is between?",
		"choice1":"8-10 months",
		"choice2":"9-10 months",
		"choice3":"8-11 months",
		"choice4":"10-11 months",
		"correct":"8-10 months"
	},
	{
		"id":"46",
		"question":"Turkeys has poor sense of smell, but has an excellent sense of?",
		"choice1":"Taste",
		"choice2":"Sight",
		"choice3":"Touch",
		"choice4":"Hearing",
		"correct":"Taste"
	},
	{
		"id":"47",
		"question":"What is the cat's extraordinary ability?",
		"choice1":"Hearing Ultrasound",
		"choice2":"Jumping",
		"choice3":"Sharp Sight",
		"choice4":"Excellent Smelling",
		"correct":"Hearing Ultrasound"
	},
	{
		"id":"48",
		"question":"What is the cat's extraordinary ability?",
		"choice1":"Hearing Ultrasound",
		"choice2":"Jumping",
		"choice3":"Sharp Sight",
		"choice4":"Excellent Smelling",
		"correct":"Hearing Ultrasound"
	},
	{
		"id":"49",
		"question":"How long can a tuna fish swim a day?",
		"choice1":"32 miles",
		"choice2":"29 miles",
		"choice3":"40 miles",
		"choice4":"36 miles",
		"correct":"40 miles"
	},
	{
		"id":"50",
		"question":"Penguins can jump _ feet out of water.",
		"choice1":"4 feet",
		"choice2":"5 feet",
		"choice3":"3 feet",
		"choice4":"6 feet",
		"correct":"6 feet"
	},
	{
		"id":"51",
		"question":"Some dogs can smell _________ under water.",
		"choice1":"Dead bodies",
		"choice2":"Bomb",
		"choice3":"Foods",
		"choice4":"Cats",
		"correct":"Dead bodies"
	},
	{
		"id":"52",
		"question":"Baby whales can gain up to ___ pounds per day.",
		"choice1":"150",
		"choice2":"200",
		"choice3":"220",
		"choice4":"250",
		"correct":"200"
	},
	{
		"id":"53",
		"question":"More than __ million turkeys are cooked and eaten in the US at Thanksgiving.",
		"choice1":"30",
		"choice2":"35",
		"choice3":"40",
		"choice4":"45",
		"correct":"45"
	},
	{
		"id":"54",
		"question":"Over how many vocal sounds does a cat have?",
		"choice1":"100",
		"choice2":"200",
		"choice3":"300",
		"choice4":"400",
		"correct":"100"
	},
	{
		"id":"55",
		"question":"How many vocal sounds does a dog have?",
		"choice1":"About 15",
		"choice2":"About 10",
		"choice3":"About 5",
		"choice4":"About 20",
		"correct":"About 10"
	},
	{
		"id":"56",
		"question":"Cat owners are __% likely to suffer an heart attack",
		"choice1":"35",
		"choice2":"30",
		"choice3":"25",
		"choice4":"20",
		"correct":"30"
	},
	{
		"id":"57",
		"question":"How long is a cheetah's lifespan up to in the wild?",
		"choice1":"10 years",
		"choice2":"11 years",
		"choice3":"12 years",
		"choice4":"13 years",
		"correct":"12 years"
	},
	{
		"id":"57",
		"question":"Fear of Spiders",
		"choice1":"Hydrophobia",
		"choice2":"Claustrophobia",
		"choice3":"Arachnophobia",
		"choice4":"Zoophobia",
		"correct":"Arachnophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"58",
		"question":"What are the world's Largest Predator?",
		"choice1":"Polar Bear",
		"choice2":"Lion",
		"choice3":"Tiger",
		"choice4":"Eagle",
		"correct":"Polar Bear"
	},
	{
		"id":"59",
		"question":"The Butterfly can see all the colors below, except?",
		"choice1":"Red",
		"choice2":"Green",
		"choice3":"Yellow",
		"choice4":"Blue",
		"correct":"Blue"
	},
	{
		"id":"60",
		"question":"What is the general name for loads of different species of fish that have yellow tails or a yellow body?",
		"choice1":"Yellow Fish",
		"choice2":"Yellow Tail",
		"choice3":"Gold Fish",
		"choice4":"Shining Fish",
		"correct":"Yellow Tail"
	},
	{
		"id":"61",
		"question":"There are roughly _____ species of butterflies.",
		"choice1":"21,000",
		"choice2":"22,000",
		"choice3":"23,000",
		"choice4":"24,000",
		"correct":"24,000"
	},
	{
		"id":"62",
		"question":"A dik-dik is a tiny antelope that lives in the following except for one.",
		"choice1":"East Africa",
		"choice2":"Namibia",
		"choice3":"Angola",
		"choice4":"Haiti",
		"correct":"Haiti"
	},
	{
		"id":"63",
		"question":"Dik-diks weigh between:",
		"choice1":"3-6 kg",
		"choice2":"4-7 kg",
		"choice3":"5-8 kg",
		"choice4":"4-9 kg",
		"correct":"3-6 kg"
	},
	{
		"id":"64",
		"question":"Female polar bears normally start having baby cubs at the age of what?",
		"choice1":"3-4 years old",
		"choice2":"4-5 years old",
		"choice3":"5-6 years old",
		"choice4":"6-7 years old",
		"correct":"4-5 years old"
	},
	{
		"id":"65",
		"question":"Fireflies are also known as?",
		"choice1":"Light Bugs",
		"choice2":"Flash Bugs",
		"choice3":"Lightning Bugs",
		"choice4":"Glowing Bugs",
		"correct":"Lightning Bugs"
	},
	{
		"id":"66",
		"question":"Dogs can see better when the light is ?",
		"choice1":"Off",
		"choice2":"Bright",
		"choice3":"Low",
		"choice4":"Dim",
		"correct":"Low"
	},
	{
		"id":"67",
		"question":"How many pet owners sleep with their pets?",
		"choice1":"73%",
		"choice2":"69%",
		"choice3":"79%",
		"choice4":"82%",
		"correct":"79%"
	},
	{
		"id":"68",
		"question":"_ dogs are among the titanic survivors.",
		"choice1":"2",
		"choice2":"3",
		"choice3":"4",
		"choice4":"5",
		"correct":"2"
	},
	{
		"id":"69",
		"question":"An owl has small _____.",
		"choice1":"Brain",
		"choice2":"Wings",
		"choice3":"Feet",
		"choice4":"Head",
		"correct":"Brain"
	},
	{
		"id":"70",
		"question":"The animal on the Firefox logo is not a fox, but a ______.",
		"choice1":"Red Dog",
		"choice2":"Red Panda",
		"choice3":"Red Cat",
		"choice4":"Tiger",
		"correct":"Red Panda"
	},
	{
		"id":"71",
		"question":"What country has the most goats in the world?",
		"choice1":"Japan",
		"choice2":"China",
		"choice3":"California",
		"choice4":"Mexico",
		"correct":"China"
	},
	{
		"id":"72",
		"question":"The average dog can run about __ mph.",
		"choice1":"20",
		"choice2":"22",
		"choice3":"19",
		"choice4":"23",
		"correct":"19"
	},
	{
		"id":"73",
		"question":"Snakes do not _____.",
		"choice1":"Blink",
		"choice2":"Breathe",
		"choice3":"Sleep",
		"choice4":"Eat",
		"correct":"Blink"
	},
	{
		"id":"74",
		"question":"A squid's eye can get as big as a _____.",
		"choice1":"Bowling Ball",
		"choice2":"Golf Ball",
		"choice3":"Basketball",
		"choice4":"Tennis Ball",
		"correct":"Basketball"
	},
	{
		"id":"75",
		"question":"Fear of Wild Animals.",
		"choice1":"Agrizoophobia",
		"choice2":"Vestiphobia",
		"choice3":"Tropophobia",
		"choice4":"Tocophobia",
		"correct":"Agrizoophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"76",
		"question":"There are over ______ types of spiders spinning their webs in the world",
		"choice1":"70,000",
		"choice2":"75,000",
		"choice3":"80,000",
		"choice4":"85,000",
		"correct":"70,000"
	},
	{
		"id":"77",
		"question":"Fear of Chickens",
		"choice1":"Claustrophobia",
		"choice2":"Celenophobia",
		"choice3":"Alektorophobia",
		"choice4":"Arachnophobia",
		"correct":"Alektorophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"78",
		"question":"How long does dogs live with humans?",
		"choice1":"13,000 years",
		"choice2":"14,000 years",
		"choice3":"15,000 years",
		"choice4":"16,000 years",
		"correct":"14,000 years"
	},
	{
		"id":"79",
		"question":"There are ____ kinds of lice in the world.",
		"choice1":"3,000",
		"choice2":"4,000",
		"choice3":"5,000",
		"choice4":"6,000",
		"correct":"3,000"
	},
	{
		"id":"80",
		"question":"How long is the life of a housefly?",
		"choice1":"12 days",
		"choice2":"14 days",
		"choice3":"16 days",
		"choice4":"18 days",
		"correct":"14 days"
	},
	{
		"id":"81",
		"question":"The lifespan of 75% of wild birds is _______.",
		"choice1":"5 months",
		"choice2":"6 months",
		"choice3":"7 months",
		"choice4":"8 months",
		"correct":"6 months"
	},
	{
		"id":"82",
		"question":"National Dance Like A Chicken Day falls on what day?",
		"choice1":"May 14",
		"choice2":"June 12",
		"choice3":"July 10",
		"choice4":"August 8",
		"correct":"May 14"
	},
	{
		"id":"83",
		"question":"What is the fastest dog on Earth?",
		"choice1":"Greyhound",
		"choice2":"Boston Terrier",
		"choice3":"Doberman",
		"choice4":"Labrador Retriever",
		"correct":"Greyhound"
	},
	{
		"id":"84",
		"question":"What is the worlds bark-less dog?",
		"choice1":"Greyhound",
		"choice2":"Boston Terrier",
		"choice3":"Doberman",
		"choice4":"Basenji",
		"correct":"Basenji"
	},
	{
		"id":"85",
		"question":"T-rex has been extinct for how many years?",
		"choice1":"65",
		"choice2":"67",
		"choice3":"69",
		"choice4":"71",
		"correct":"65"
	},
	{
		"id":"86",
		"question":"The oldest recorded elephant lived for how many years?",
		"choice1":"70",
		"choice2":"78",
		"choice3":"82",
		"choice4":"86",
		"correct":"82"
	},
	{
		"id":"87",
		"question":"According to the records, how many monkeys are there in the world?",
		"choice1":"50 million",
		"choice2":"60 million",
		"choice3":"70 million",
		"choice4":"80 million",
		"correct":"50 million"
	},
	{
		"id":"88",
		"question":"There are an estimated ___________ dogs in the world.",
		"choice1":"400 million",
		"choice2":"600 million",
		"choice3":"800 million",
		"choice4":"1 billion",
		"correct":"400 million"
	},
	{
		"id":"89",
		"question":"What were the first animal to be used for milk by humans?",
		"choice1":"Goat",
		"choice2":"Cow",
		"choice3":"Carabao",
		"choice4":"Sheep",
		"correct":"Goat"
	},
	{
		"id":"90",
		"question":"What is the other term for a baby goat?",
		"choice1":"Lad",
		"choice2":"Kid",
		"choice3":"Buck",
		"choice4":"Doe",
		"correct":"Kid"
	},
	{
		"id":"91",
		"question":"Fear of cats.",
		"choice1":"Ailurophobia",
		"choice2":"Nekophobia",
		"choice3":"Claustrophobia",
		"choice4":"Catophobia",
		"correct":"Ailurophobia"
	},
	{
		"id":"92",
		"question":"How much larger are female bald eagles than the male ones.",
		"choice1":"20%",
		"choice2":"35%",
		"choice3":"25%",
		"choice4":"40%",
		"correct":"25%"
	},
	{
		"id":"93",
		"question":"How far does the adult lion's roar reach?",
		"choice1":"3 miles",
		"choice2":"5 miles",
		"choice3":"7 miles",
		"choice4":"9 miles",
		"correct":"5 miles"
	},
	{
		"id":"94",
		"question":"Over how many breeds of goats are there in the world?",
		"choice1":"170",
		"choice2":"190",
		"choice3":"210",
		"choice4":"230",
		"correct":"210"
	},
	{
		"id":"95",
		"question":"How many times is the tiger's eye sharper at night?",
		"choice1":"9",
		"choice2":"8",
		"choice3":"7",
		"choice4":"6",
		"correct":"6"
	},
	{
		"id":"96",
		"question":"What do you call the group of whale?",
		"choice1":"Army",
		"choice2":"Herd",
		"choice3":"Peer",
		"choice4":"Pod",
		"correct":"Pod"
	},
	{
		"id":"97",
		"question":"How much food can a male gorilla eat a day?",
		"choice1":"20 pounds",
		"choice2":"30 pounds",
		"choice3":"40 pounds",
		"choice4":"50 pounds",
		"correct":"40 pounds"
	},
	{
		"id":"98",
		"question":"What kind of animal is Pikachu?",
		"choice1":"Cat",
		"choice2":"Dog",
		"choice3":"Mouse",
		"choice4":"Panda",
		"correct":"Mouse"
	},
	{
		"id":"99",
		"question":"Jelly fish is composed of __ water",
		"choice1":"95%",
		"choice2":"96%",
		"choice3":"97%",
		"choice4":"98%",
		"correct":"98%"
	}]
	
		